{
    "subject": "resource/Edinho_Campos",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Brazil",
    "human_readable": "Edinho Campos was born in Brazil.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8851480484008789,
            "question": "Where was Edinho Campos born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8682286143302917,
            "question": "Is Edinho Campos Brazilian?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.632889449596405,
            "question": "Are there any interesting facts about Edinho Campos's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5048097372055054,
            "question": "What country is associated with Edinho Campos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4985780715942383,
            "question": "What is Edinho Campos known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34654662013053894,
            "question": "Where might Edinho Campos currently reside?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3339875340461731,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Edinho Campos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2974434494972229,
            "question": "Does Edinho Campos have any notable achievements?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1510952264070511,
            "question": "Who are some other famous people from Brazil?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09832897782325745,
            "question": "What is the culture like in Brazil?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Edinho Campos was born in Brazil.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3392_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some other famous people from Brazil?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3392_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Edinho Campos have any notable achievements?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3392_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Edinho Campos?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3392_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3392_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3392_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3392_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3392_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3392_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3392_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3392_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3392_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3392_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3392_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Edimo Ferreira Campos (known as Edinho) is a well-known figure in Brazil's sports industry and was born on February 27, 1970, in Santos, S\u00e3o Paulo. Both facts support the query that Edinho Campos was born in Brazil."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}